Gregg Brown

Experienced Revenue Assurance Analyst with a demonstrated history of working in Telecoms and Financial regulated industries.

Skilled in Trend Analysis, Service Delivery, and Reconciling Reports.

Strong analyst professional with a focus on Automation and Software Development. Highly motivated, unafraid of a challenge with a pro-active attitude, a real team player.

Contact

Address

123 Whitelaw Drive Bathgate West Lothian EH48 1RR

Tel:

o1506 792645 (Work) o7887 854191 (Mobile)

Email

gregg.brown@sky.uk gregg.p.brown@gmail.com

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/gregapbrown

GitHub

github.com/gregg-brown-skyuk

Skills

Data Analysis

Customer Experience

Project Delivery

Process Automation

Service Improvement

Data Visualisation

Software

MS Excel

MS Access

VS Code SharePoint

Office 365

UiPath Studio

UiPath Orchestrator

Google Cloud (BigQuery)

Programming

VBA

SQL

M

Python

JavaScript

HTML₅

CSS

XPATH

XML

JSON

Education

Inveralmond Community High School, Livingston

May 1998

- 7 Standard Grades, 4 Higher Grades, 2 CSYS Grades

Heriot-Watt University, Edinburgh

May 2000

- Certificate of Higher Education in Mathematics and Physics

Online Learning Certification

Continuous

- Various topics incl. SQL & Python for Data Science, OOP, and UiPath

Work Experience

Cost Assurance Analyst

January 2022-Present

Sky TV - Livingston

- Provided analysis support to Operational teams, ensuring adherence to all regulatory and compliance requirements are being met.
- Managed costs associated with services to ensure validity prior to payment.
- Identified revenue leakage and putting in place corrective measures.
- Liaised with internal business teams and 3rd party providers.
- Designed and implemented process improvements and putting in place controls and measures to analyse performance.

Billing Analyst (Revenue Assurance)

June 2014-December 2021

Sky TV - Livingston

- Reconciled customers' billings across customer management and billing systems.
- Investigated and resolved exceptions and escalations in a timely manner.
- Reviewed and monitored processes and procedures.
- Influenced change, supported projects, and managed stakeholder expectations.
- Developed SQL queries for interrogation of databases.
- Developed several automation solutions for reconciliation teams reporting tasks with an annual time saving of over 320 hours.

Sky Talk Reconciliation Clerk

August 2012-June 2014

Sky TV - Livingston

- Ensured successful rating & billing of calls and telephony products.
- Completed reporting in a rigorous and timely manner

Customer Advisor, Contact Centre

October 2009-August 2012

Sky TV - Livingston

- Handled TV, Broadband and Sky Talk installation and billing enquiries.
- Provided technical assistance for TV equipment and online services.

Corporate Online Support

October 2005-October 2009

Bank of Scotland - Edinburgh

- User acceptance testing of new online transaction environments.
- Production of Regression and User Acceptance test scripts.
- Identify enhancements to online services & Help Team support.
- Stakeholder management with Test and Implementation Managers.

Customer Account Administrator

June 2000-October 2005

Intelligent Finance - Livingston

Various positions held within the business including Direct Sales, Application Fulfilment, Credit Control and Contact Centre Resource Area.